{
    "subject": "Nigel_Cole",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Kate_Isitt",
    "human_readable": "Nigel Cole is married to Kate Isitt.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883412718772888,
            "question": "Is Kate Isitt married to Nigel Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9835925102233887,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9206753373146057,
            "question": "Who is Nigel Cole married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8761999011039734,
            "question": "To whom is Kate Isitt married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8431177139282227,
            "question": "Based on the statement, are Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt in a romantic relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8064374923706055,
            "question": "What is the nature of the relationship between Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7028287053108215,
            "question": "What is the name of Nigel Cole's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6835049390792847,
            "question": "What is the link described between Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6766873598098755,
            "question": "If you were to describe the familial connection between Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt, what would you say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20465947687625885,
            "question": "Name the individuals involved in a marital relationship according to this statement."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nigel Cole is married to Kate Isitt.",
            "html": "yago_13087_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to describe the familial connection between Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt, what would you say?",
            "html": "yago_13087_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the link described between Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt?",
            "html": "yago_13087_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Nigel Cole's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_13087_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13087_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the triple, as there are multiple mentions of Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt being married. The exact date (2000) and year they got together (1998) also confirm this information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt are married. For example, the document `66.txt` states: \"Nigel Cole and Kate Isitt have been married for 24 years.\" Another document (`5.txt`) confirms their marriage date: \"She has been married to Nigel Cole since January 1, 2000.\" Therefore, the triple \"Nigel Cole is married to Kate Isitt\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}